Lesson 2  A Day at the Sea
海での一日
先週の日曜日のことでした。
It was last Sunday.
家族とわたしは海へ行きました。
My family and I went to the sea.
海は青くてきれいでした。
The sea was blue and beautiful.
太陽は明るく、空には雲がありませんでした。
The sun was bright,
and there were no clouds in the sky.
兄は泳ぐのがとても上手でした。
My brother was very good at swimming.
何度も水に入り、とてもうれしそうでした。
He went into the water many times,
and he was very happy.
妹とわたしは浜辺にいました。
My sister and I were on the beach.
わたしたちは一日中いっしょでした。
We were together all day.
昼食には、母が作ったパンと魚を食べました。
For lunch, we had bread and fish
that my mother made.
とてもおいしかったです。
They were delicious.
夕方には少し疲れていましたが、心はとても満たされていました。
In the evening, we were a little tired,
but our hearts were very full.